Welcome to the GO programming for Beginners by course, if you're looking to learn about
a powerful and increasingly popular programming language, you come to the right place.
This course is designed to get you up and running with GO, also known as GO Link from the
ground up.
We'll cover the fundamentals, help you understand its core concepts, and equip you with
the skills to start building your own applications.
This course will cover the following essential topics.
The GO CLI will introduce you to the GO command line interface, showing you how to
compile and run your GO programs.
Packages and modules.
You'll learn how GO organizes code and manages dependencies, which are crucial for structuring
any GO project.
Variables and data types.
You'll discover how to store and manipulate different kinds of information in your GO programs.
Functions and flow control.
We'll understand how to define reusable blocks of code and direct the execution path of
your programs using conditionals and loops.
You'll learn how to create custom data types to group related information into a single
organized unit called a structure.
Arrays and maps.
We'll explore how to work with collections of data using fixed size arrays, slices, and
key value maps.
This bike course is just a slice of my larger GO boot camp course.
If you're enjoying the simplicity of GO and want to learn more, be sure to check that out
as well.
Alright, let's GO!